<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetup on I2P - The Invisible Internet Project</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/categories/meetup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetup on I2P - The Invisible Internet Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/categories/meetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I2P at BSidesNYC</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/02/12/i2p-at-bsidesnyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/02/12/i2p-at-bsidesnyc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sadie and str4d attended BSidesNYC on Saturday January 20th. Thank you to the BSides Team for setting such a great conference!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aside from a few talks, we mostly worked on several goals that we had set for the day during the afternoon in the common area at John Jay College.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our most pressing task was writing the high-level roadmap for 2018, following the discussions at 34C3. This has &lt;a href=&#34;../../../blog/2018/02/11/high-level-roadmap-for-2018/&#34;&gt;now been posted&lt;/a&gt; - go check it out! We also picked up some communication threads that were put aside over the holiday period around our nascent Vulnerability Response Process, and getting it into &amp;ldquo;production use&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2PCon: Mission Accomplished</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/08/20/i2pcon-mission-accomplished/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/08/20/i2pcon-mission-accomplished/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2PCon has been a giant success. For us, the I2P contributors, it represents a leap forward in terms of what we&amp;rsquo;re capable of pulling off as a community, how we communicate the usecases of I2P and reach out to privacy conscious individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By arranging this event, we&amp;rsquo;ve also grown our community. People who&amp;rsquo;ve previously only lurked on our irc channels, or run our software or possibly hadn&amp;rsquo;t even heard of I2P are now a part of our community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2PCon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/07/16/i2pcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/07/16/i2pcon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2PCon is the first event of its kind. It has two short term goals. Where the first one is to provide the general public with an event where knowledge about privacy and privacy concerns can be obtained. The second goal is to further the I2P project and its community. This will take the shape of technical discussions about cryptography, anonymity and I2P centric topics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a larger and more long-term goal of this event, and it is to build a community of privacy-conscious individuals. By connecting people who recognize the importance of privacy, we would like to provide a forum where this community can grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
