<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release on I2P - The Invisible Internet Project</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/categories/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release on I2P - The Invisible Internet Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/categories/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.10.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/09/08/i2p-2.10.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/09/08/i2p-2.10.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Work continues on the implementation and deployment of post-quantum cryptography in I2P. In this release post-quantum cryptography is available but not turned on by default for new tunnels. Those of you interested in testing post-quantum support should enable it via the &amp;ldquo;Hidden Service Manager&amp;rdquo; under &amp;ldquo;Encryption Types.&amp;rdquo; Be sure to get in touch on #i2p-dev in IRC2P for help and to report any issues you encounter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2PSnark now supports UDP trackers. This should help the network overall by reducing the load of torrent trackers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.9.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/06/02/i2p-2.9.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/06/02/i2p-2.9.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P 2.9.0 is a maintenance release that includes bug fixes and work on new features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-new&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s New&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thread usage has been improved to improve the performance of the i2ptunnel system. NTCP2 has been improved to resist probing attacks. The notification system has been integrated into more applications to provide better feedback to users from I2PSnark and the other applications. Automatic floodfill enrollment has been fixed. Users may observe increased resource usage when acting as floodfill. If this is not desired, floodfill mode can be disabled on the /config page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.8.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/03/29/i2p-2.8.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/03/29/i2p-2.8.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2.8.2 fixes a bug causing SHA256 failures that was introduced in the 2.8.1 release. The bug primarily affects high-bandwidth routers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix SHA256 double-free from Noise&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Clear i2ptunnel bubble count when clearing status messages&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-improvements&#34;&gt;Other Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduce memory usage in BanlistRenderer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use torrent name instead of torrent file name in notifications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;7658f9ba7e28ab29ffeb3ec1909bf04f5ae391ee159980145ea01bd793c46f80  i2pinstall_2.8.2_windows.exe&#xA;cd606827a9bca363bd6b3c89664772ec211d276cce3148f207643cc5e5949b8a  i2pinstall_2.8.2.jar&#xA;039b59fedd4a64aaeb6b74ab974310abdc9c08cb47ef1b8568c718965b50a485  i2psource_2.8.2.tar.bz2&#xA;71cef41d7184516e42c15dc5105e52ab19960affd571b636e767e8bf8c227075  i2pupdate_2.8.2.zip&#xA;15d886a9015dcf27ccc25e31b703ef6538b8b777176adf643dfe8ee0ba4984e0  i2pupdate.su3&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.8.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/03/17/2.8.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/03/17/2.8.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2.8.1 fixes accesses to local sites that were broken in 2.8.0.&#xA;We have added notification bubbles to several applications in the console to highlight application messages.&#xA;We fixed a tunnel test bug that may have been affecting tunnel reliability.&#xA;The addressbook now has a new &amp;ldquo;latest&amp;rdquo; tab that displays the newest hostnames added from your subscriptions.&#xA;There are several dark theme fixes and improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We fixed the installer that previously failed on Java 21 or higher.&#xA;We also fixed installing to directory paths that contain spaces on Linux.&#xA;For those of you that use Docker, we updated outdated Docker container and container libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.8.0 Released</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/02/04/i2p-2.8.0-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2025/02/04/i2p-2.8.0-released/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release improves I2P by fixing bugs, removing unused code, and improving network stability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have improved handling of congested routers in the network.&#xA;Issues in UPnP and NAT traversal were addressed to improve connectivity and error reporting.&#xA;We now have a more aggressive strategy for leaseset removal from the NetDb to improve router performance and mitigate overload.&#xA;Other changes were implemented to reduce the observability of events like a router rebooting or shutting down.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.7.0 Released</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/10/09/i2p-2.7.0-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/10/09/i2p-2.7.0-released/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release, I2P 2.7.0, continues our work by fixing bugs, improving performance, and adding features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Access to information from the console and applications has been improved.&#xA;Issues have been fixed in I2PSnark and SusiMail search.&#xA;The netDB search embedded into the router console now operates in a more intuitive and useful way.&#xA;Minor improvements have been made to diagnostic displays in advanced mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bugs have also been fixed to improve compatibility within the network.&#xA;An issue with publishing leaseSets was solved which improves reliability major hidden services.&#xA;I2PSnark no longer changes the infohash when a user changes only the trackers on an existing torrent.&#xA;This prevents torrents from being unnecessarily disrupted by these changes.&#xA;We welcomed this contribution from a new contributor.&#xA;A conflict in the handling of a streaming library option was resolved to improve compatibility with other I2P implementations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.6.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/08/06/2.6.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/08/06/2.6.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P 2.6.1 is released in order to fix a User-Interface bug in the Hidden Services Manager application.&#xA;This bug caused scrolling to be disabled, rendering some configuration inaccessible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release.&#xA;The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;changes&#34;&gt;Changes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Graphs: render graphs in svg&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translations: generate internal translation leaderboard&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2ptunnel: Fix bug causing truncation configuration UI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://git.idk.i2p/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/-/issues?scope=all&amp;amp;state=closed&amp;amp;milestone_title=2.6.1&#34;&gt;Full list of fixed bugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.6.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/07/19/i2p-2.6.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/07/19/i2p-2.6.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release, I2P 2.6.0, continues our work by fixing bugs, adding features, and improving the network&amp;rsquo;s reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Newer routers will be favored when selecting floodfill routers.&#xA;I2PSnark received features which improve the performance of PeX(Peer Exchange), in addition to bug fixes.&#xA;Legacy transport protocols are being removed, simplifying the code in the UDP transports.&#xA;Locally-hosted destination will be reachable by local clients without requesting their LeaseSet, improving performance and testability.&#xA;Additional tweaks were made to peer selection strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.5.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/05/15/2.5.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/05/15/2.5.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P 2.5.2 is released to fix a bug introduced in 2.5.0 causing truncation of some HTTP content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release.&#xA;The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;changes&#34;&gt;Changes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Console: Update rrd4j to 3.9.1-preview&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Router: Publish G cap if symmetric natted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2ptunnel: Fix bug causing truncation of some HTTP content&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2ptunnel: Fix custom option form width (light theme)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tunnels: Fix selection of peers with expired RIs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://git.idk.i2p/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/-/issues?scope=all&amp;amp;state=closed&amp;amp;milestone_title=2.5.2&#34;&gt;Full list of fixed bugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Release I2P 2.5.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/05/06/new-release-i2p-2.5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/05/06/new-release-i2p-2.5.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P 2.5.1 is being released to address Denial-of-Service Attacks affecting the I2P network and services.&#xA;With this release we disable the IP-based parts of the Sybil attack detection tool which were targeted to amplify the effect and duration of the attack.&#xA;This should help the network return to normal operation.&#xA;Those of you who have disabled the Sybil attack detection tool may safely re-enable it.&#xA;Adjustments to other subsystems to improve RouterInfo validation and peer selection have also been made.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Weather</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/04/25/stormy-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/04/25/stormy-weather/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The I2P network is currently under a Denial-of-Service attack.&#xA;This attack affects I2P and i2pd but in different ways and is having a serious effect on network health.&#xA;Reachability of I2P sites is badly degraded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are hosting a service inside I2P and it is hosted on a Floodfill router, you should consider multihoming the service on a Floodfill-disabled router to improve reachability.&#xA;Other mitigations are being discussed but a long-term, backward-compatible solution is still being worked on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Release I2P 2.5.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/04/08/new-release-i2p-2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2024/04/08/new-release-i2p-2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release, I2P 2.5.0, provides more user-facing improvements than the 2.4.0 release, which was focused on implementing the NetDB isolation strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New features have been added to I2PSnark like the ability to search through torrents.&#xA;Bugs have been fixed to improve compatibility with other I2P torrent clients like BiglyBT and qBittorrent.&#xA;We would like to thank all of the developers who have worked with libtorrent and qBittorrent to enable and improve their I2P support.&#xA;New features have also been added to SusiMail including support for Markdown formatting in emails and the ability to drag-and-drop attachments into emails.&#xA;Tunnels created with the Hidden Services manager now support &amp;ldquo;Keepalive&amp;rdquo; which improves performance and compatibility with web technologies, enabling more sophisticated I2P sites.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 2.4.0 Release with Congestion and NetDB Security improvements</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/12/18/i2p-2.4.0-release-with-congestion-and-netdb-security-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/12/18/i2p-2.4.0-release-with-congestion-and-netdb-security-improvements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release, I2P 2.4.0, continues our effort to improve the security and stability of the I2P network.&#xA;It contains significant improvements to the Network Database, an essential structure within the I2P network used for disovering your peers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The congestion handling changes will improve network stability by giving routers the ability to relieve congested peers by avoiding them.&#xA;This will help the network limit the effect of tunnel spam.&#xA;It will also help the network heal during and after DDoS attacks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy-Install for Windows 2.3.0 Released</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/07/10/easy-install-for-windows-2.3.0-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/07/10/easy-install-for-windows-2.3.0-released/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The I2P Easy-Install bundle for Windows version 2.3.0 has now been released.&#xA;As usual, this release includes an updated version of the I2P router.&#xA;This extends to security issues which affect people hosting services on the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will be the last release of the Easy-Install bundle which will be incompatible with the I2P Desktop GUI.&#xA;It has been updated to include new versions of all included webextensions.&#xA;A longstanding bug in I2P in Private Browsing which makes it incompatible with custom themes has been fixed.&#xA;Users are still advised to &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; install custom themes.&#xA;Snark tabs are not automatically pinned to the top of the tab order in Firefox.&#xA;Except for using alternate cookieStores, Snark tabs now behave as normal browser tabs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P Release 2.3.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/06/25/i2p-release-2.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/06/25/i2p-release-2.3.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release contains fixes for CVE-2023-36325.&#xA;CVE-2023-36325 is a context-confusion bug which occurred in the bloom filter.&#xA;An attacker crafts an I2NP message containing a unique messageID, and sends that messageID to a client.&#xA;The message, after passing through the bloom filter, is not allowed to be re-used in a second message.&#xA;The attacker then sends the same message directly to the router.&#xA;The router passes the message to the bloom filter, and is dropped.&#xA;This leaks the information that the messageID has been seen before, giving the attacker a strong reason to believe that the router is hosting the client.&#xA;This has been fixed by separting the bloom filter&amp;rsquo;s functionality into different contexts based on whether a message came down a client tunnel, an exploratory tunnel, was sent to the router directly.&#xA;Under normal circumstances, this attack takes several days to perform successfully and may be confounded by several factors such as routers restarting during the attack phase and sensitivity to false-positives.&#xA;Users of Java I2P are recommended to update immediately to avoid the attack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P Release 2.2.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/04/12/i2p-release-2.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/04/12/i2p-release-2.2.1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After the I2P 2.2.0 release, which was moved forward to accelerate mitigations for the DDOS attacks, we learned about a few developing issues which made it necessary to build and release new packages.&#xA;This release fixes an issue within Ubuntu Lunar and Debian Sid where the router console was inaccessible using an updated version of the jakarta package.&#xA;Docker packages were not reading arguments correctly, resulting in inaccessible configuration files.&#xA;This issue has also been resolved.&#xA;The docker container is now also compatible with Podman.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P Release 2.2.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/03/13/i2p-release-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/03/13/i2p-release-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have elected to move forward the 2.2.0 release date, which will be occurring today, March 13, 2023.&#xA;This release includes a changes across the NetDB, Floodfill, and Peer-Selection components which improve the ability of the router to survive DDOS attacks.&#xA;The attacks are likely to continue, but the improvements to these systems will help to mitigate the risk of DDOS attacks by helping the router identify and de-prioritize routers that appear malicious.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the recent Denial of Service attacks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/02/09/about-the-recent-denial-of-service-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/02/09/about-the-recent-denial-of-service-attacks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The I2P network is currently being affected by a Denial of Service attack.&#xA;The floodfill function of the network has been affected, resulting in responses being disrupted and tunnel build success rates dropping.&#xA;Participants in the network have experienced difficulties connecting to I2P sites and using I2P services.&#xA;Mitigation strategies are being investigated and implemented gradually.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the attack has degraded performance, the network remains intact and usable.&#xA;Java I2P routers appear to be handling the issues better than i2pd routers for now.&#xA;Various mitigations should begin to appear in dev builds of both Java and C++ routers in the next week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update on Mac Easy Install Notarization</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/31/update-on-mac-easy-install-notarization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/31/update-on-mac-easy-install-notarization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The I2P Easy-Install Bundle for Mac has been experiencing stalled updates for the past 2 releases due to the departure of its maintainer.&#xA;It is recommended that users of the Easy-Install bundle for Mac switch to the classic java-style installer which was recently restored to the download page.&#xA;1.9.0 has known security issues and is not suitable for hosting services or any long-term use. Users are advised to migrate away as soon as possible.&#xA;Advanced users of the Easy-Install bundle may work around this by compiling the bundle from source and self-signing the software.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Easy-Install 2.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/13/windows-easy-install-2.1.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/13/windows-easy-install-2.1.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The I2P Easy-Install bundle for Windows version 2.1.0 has been released.&#xA;As usual, this release includes an updated version of the I2P Router.&#xA;This release of I2P provides improved strategies for dealing with network congestion.&#xA;These should improve performance, connectivity, and secure the long-term health of the I2P network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release features mostly under-the-hood improvements to the browser profile launcher.&#xA;Compatibility with Tor Browser Bundle has been improved by enabling TBB configuration through environment variables.&#xA;The Firefox profile has been updated, an the base versions of the extensions have been updated.&#xA;Improvements have been made throughout the codebase and the deployment process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/09/2.1.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2023/01/09/2.1.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have learned several things since our 2.0.0 release in November.&#xA;As routers have updated to that release, the network has gone from about 1% to over 60% support for our new SSU2 transport protocol.&#xA;First, we have confirmed that SSU2 is a solid, well designed, and secure protocol.&#xA;Second, however, we have found and fixed numerous minor or rarely-triggered bugs in the implementation of the protocol.&#xA;Cumulatively, the effects of these bugs have reduced the performance of the network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Install 2.0.0 for Windows, OSX delayed by 1 Month</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/11/23/easy-install-2.0.0-for-windows-osx-delayed-by-1-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/11/23/easy-install-2.0.0-for-windows-osx-delayed-by-1-month/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The I2P Easy-Install bundle for Windows has been released.&#xA;In this release, support has been added for most major browsers, including all major Firefox(Gecko) and Chromium forks.&#xA;Compatibility with external I2P Service installs and un-bundled I2P user installs has been improved.&#xA;The Easy-Install bundle can now detect other I2P routers and prompt the user to launch them instead, if they already have I2P.&#xA;The browser extensions have been updated to the latest versions.&#xA;The Easy-Install now has access to &lt;code&gt;i2p.plugins.firefox&lt;/code&gt;&amp;rsquo;s usability mode via the &lt;code&gt;-usability&lt;/code&gt; command-line flag.&#xA;The default mode is the &amp;ldquo;Strict&amp;rdquo; mode where Javascript is disabled by NoScript.&#xA;In usability mode, Javascript is restricted by JShelter.&#xA;For more details, see the profile manager repository at i2pgit.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.0.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/11/21/2.0.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/11/21/2.0.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P release 2.0.0 enables our new UDP transport SSU2 for all users, after completion of minor features, testing, and numerous bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We also have fixes all over, including for the installer, network database, adding to the private address book, the Windows browser launcher, and IPv6 UPnP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to&#xA;maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Easy-Install Bundle 1.9.5 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/09/07/windows-easy-install-bundle-1.9.5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/09/07/windows-easy-install-bundle-1.9.5-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;bug-fixing-release-for-windows-11-users&#34;&gt;Bug Fixing release for Windows 11 users&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This point release includes a bug fix in the included I2P router, which resolves a highly obscure bug where the context clock is out of sync with the clock in use by the File System, resulting in a router which is unable to read the current state of it&amp;rsquo;s own NetDB. Although this bug has only been observed on Windows 11 so far, it is highly recommended that all users update to the new build.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Easy-Install Bundle 1.9.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/08/28/windows-easy-install-bundle-1.9.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/08/28/windows-easy-install-bundle-1.9.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-update-includes-the-new-190-router-and-major-quality-of-life-improvements-for-bundle-users&#34;&gt;This update includes the new 1.9.0 router and major quality-of-life improvements for bundle users&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release includes the new I2P 1.9.0 router and is based on Java 18.02.1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The old batch scripts have been phased out in favor of a more flexible and stable solution in the jpackage itself. This should fix all bugs related to path-finding and path-quoting which were present in the batch scripts. After you upgrade, the batch scripts can be safely deleted. They will be removed by the installer in the next update.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.9.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/08/22/1.9.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/08/22/1.9.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have spent the last three months working on our new UDP transport protocol &amp;ldquo;SSU2&amp;rdquo; with a small number of volunteer testers. This release completes the implementation, including relay and peer testing. We are enabling it by default for Android and ARM platforms, and a small percentage of other routers at random. This will allow us to do much more testing in the next three months, finish the connection migration feature, and fix any remaining issues. We plan to enable it for everyone in the next release scheduled for November. No manual configuration is necessary. Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s the usual collection of bug fixes in this release as well. We also added an automatic deadlock detector that has already found a rare deadlock that is now fixed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.8.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/05/23/1.8.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/05/23/1.8.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release includes bug fixes in i2psnark, the router, I2CP, and UPnP. Router fixes address bugs in soft restart, IPv6, SSU peer testing, network database stores, and tunnel building. Router family handling and Sybil classification have also been significantly improved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together with i2pd, we are developing our new UDP transport, SSU2. SSU2 will bring substantial performance and security improvements. It will also allow us to finally replace our last usage of the very slow ElGamal encryption, completing the full cryptography upgrade we started about 9 years ago. This release contains a preliminary implementation which is disabled by default. If you wish to participate in testing, please look for current information on zzz.i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jpackage Update for Java CVE-2022-21449</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/04/21/jpackage-update-for-java-cve-2022-21449/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/04/21/jpackage-update-for-java-cve-2022-21449/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New I2P Easy-Install bundles have been generated using the latest release of the Java Virtual Machine which contains a fix for CVE-2022-21449 &amp;ldquo;Psychic Signatures.&amp;rdquo; It is recommended that users of the easy-install bundles update as soon as possible. Current OSX users will recieve updates automatically, Windows users should download the installer from our downloads page and run the installer normally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The I2P router on Linux uses the Java Virtual Machine configured by the host system. Users on those platforms should downgrade to a stable Java version below Java 14 in order to mitigate the vulnerability until updates are released by the package maintainers. Other users using an external JVM should update the JVM to a fixed version as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.7.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/02/21/1.7.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2022/02/21/1.7.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 1.7.0 release contains several performance and reliability improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are now popup messages in the system tray, for those platforms that support it. i2psnark has a new torrent editor. The NTCP2 transport now uses much less CPU.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The long-deprecated BOB interface is removed for new installs. It will continue to work in existing installs, except for Debian packages. Any remaining users of BOB applications should ask the developers to convert to the SAMv3 protocol.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.6.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/11/29/1.6.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/11/29/1.6.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: 1.6.1 is the current release. 1.6.0 was tagged but not released.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release completes the rollout of two major protocol updates developed in 2021. The transition to X25519 encryption for routers is accelerated, and we expect almost all routers to be rekeyed by the end of the year. Short tunnel build messages are enabled for a significant bandwidth reduction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We added a theme selection panel to the new install wizard. We&amp;rsquo;ve improved SSU performance and fixed an issue with SSU peer test messages. The tunnel build Bloom filter was adjusted to reduce memory usage. We have enhanced support for non-Java plugins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5.0 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/08/23/1.5.0-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/08/23/1.5.0-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s right, after 9 years of 0.9.x releases, we are going straight from 0.9.50 to 1.5.0. This does not signify a major API change, or a claim that development is now complete. It is simply a recognition of almost 20 years of work to provide anonymity and security for our users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release finishes implementation of smaller tunnel build messages to reduce bandwidth. We continue the transition of the network&amp;rsquo;s routers to X25519 encryption. Of course there are also numerous bug fixes and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.50 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/05/17/0.9.50-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/05/17/0.9.50-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.50 continues the transition to ECIES-X25519 for router encryption keys. We have enabled DNS over HTTPS for reseeding to protect users from passive DNS snooping. There are numerous fixes and improvements for IPv6 addresses, including new UPnP support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have finally fixed some longstanding SusiMail corruption bugs. Changes to the bandwidth limiter should improve network tunnel performance. There are several improvements in our Docker containers. We have improved our defenses for possible malicious and buggy routers in the network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.49 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/02/17/0.9.49-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2021/02/17/0.9.49-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.49 continues the work to make I2P faster and more secure. We have several improvements and fixes for the SSU (UDP) transport that should result in faster speeds. This release also starts the migration to new, faster ECIES-X25519 encryption for routers. (Destinations have been using this encryption for a few releases now) We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on the specifications and protocols for new encryption for several years, and we are getting close to the end of it! The migration will take several releases to complete.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.48 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/11/30/0.9.48-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/11/30/0.9.48-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.48 enables our new end-to-end encryption protocol (proposal 144) for most services. We have added preliminary support for new tunnel build message encryption (proposal 152). There are significant performance improvements throughout the router.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Packages for Ubuntu Xenial (16.04 LTS) are no longer supported. Users on that platform should upgrade so you may continue to receive I2P updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.47 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/08/24/0.9.47-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/08/24/0.9.47-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.47 enables our new end-to-end encryption protocol (proposal 144) by default for some services. The Sybil analysis and blocking tool is now enabled by default.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 8 or higher is now required. Debian packages for Wheezy and Stretch, and for Ubuntu Trusty and Precise, are no longer supported. Users on those platforms should upgrade so you may continue to receive I2P updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.46 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/05/25/0.9.46-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/05/25/0.9.46-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.46 contains significant performance improvements in the streaming library. We have completed development of ECIES encryption (proposal 144) and there is now an option to enable it for testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows users only&lt;/strong&gt;: This release fixes a local privilege escalation vulnerability which could be exploited by a local user that has the ability to run programs. Please apply the update as soon as possible. Thanks to Blaze Infosec for their responsible disclosure of the issue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.45 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/02/25/0.9.45-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2020/02/25/0.9.45-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.45 contains important fixes for hidden mode and the bandwidth tester. There&amp;rsquo;s an update to the console dark theme. We continue work on improving performance and the development of new end-to-end encryption (proposal 144).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dark theme improvements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Console icon changes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Move some translations from console to router and core for embedded uses&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Jetty 9.2.29&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tomcat 8.5.50&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2psnark HTML5 preview player for partial files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.44 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/12/01/0.9.44-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/12/01/0.9.44-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.44 contains an important fix for a denial of service issue in hidden services handling of new encryption types. All users should update as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The release includes initial support for new end-to-end encryption (proposal 144). Work continues on this project, and it is not yet ready for use. There are changes to the console home page, and new embedded HTML5 media players in i2psnark. Additional fixes for firewalled IPv6 networks are included. Tunnel build fixes should result in faster startup for some users.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.43 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/10/22/0.9.43-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/10/22/0.9.43-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the 0.9.43 release, we continue work on stronger security and privacy features and performance improvements. Our implementation of the new leaseset specification (LS2) is now complete. We are beginning our implementation of stronger and faster end-to-end encryption (proposal 144) for a future release. Several IPv6 address detection issues have been fixed, and there of course are several other bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.42 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/08/27/0.9.42-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/08/27/0.9.42-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.42 continues the work to make I2P faster and more reliable. It includes several changes to speed up our UDP transport. We have split up the configuration files to enable future work for more modular packaging. We continue work to implement new proposals for faster and more secure encryption. There are, of course, a lot of bug fixes also.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.41 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/07/02/0.9.41-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/07/02/0.9.41-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.41 includes performance improvements, streaming library enhancements, and important bug fixes. We continue development work on new leasesets (LS2) and encrypted leasesets. The release contains the usual assortment of bug fixes and translation updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.40 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/05/07/0.9.40-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/05/07/0.9.40-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.40 disables the old NTCP1 transport and removes support for SSU introductions over IPv6. Now that NTCP2 has been enabled by default for over 6 months, it&amp;rsquo;s time to disable the old NTCP1 transport and save bandwidth and memory. We continue development work on LS2 and encrypted leasesets. Several bugs have been fixed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.39 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/03/21/0.9.39-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/03/21/0.9.39-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.39 includes extensive changes for new network database types (proposal 123). The i2pcontrol plugin is now bundled as a web-app to support development of RPC applications. Several important bugs in streaming, i2psnark, and NTCP2 have been fixed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.38 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/01/22/0.9.38-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2019/01/22/0.9.38-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.38 enables NTCP2 by default for all users. NTCP2 provides effective resistance against DPI censorship and results in reduced CPU load because of the faster, modern cryptography used. The release also includes important bug fixes and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.37 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/10/04/0.9.37-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/10/04/0.9.37-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.37 continues work on our new transport NTCP2, which was introduced in the previous release. A new SSU IPv6 peer testing protocol is now supported. The release contains numerous bug fixes and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.36 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/08/23/0.9.36-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/08/23/0.9.36-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.36 introduces NTCP2, our new secure transport protocol. NTCP2 provides effective resistance against DPI censorship and results in reduced CPU load. It makes I2P more likely to run on low-end devices such as smartphones and home routers. The protocol is disabled by default in this release for testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.35 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/06/26/0.9.35-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/06/26/0.9.35-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.35 changes the default signature type to Ed25519. This is the final step in the long process of migrating to newer, stronger, and faster cryptography. The release includes numerous bug fixes and performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.34 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/04/10/0.9.34-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/04/10/0.9.34-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.34 includes important bug fixes for hidden services, streaming, and SAM. The release continues work on preparation for Ed25519 as the default signature type and NTCP2 as a new transport. Performance improvements and the usual assortment of bug fixes are included.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.33 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/01/30/0.9.33-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2018/01/30/0.9.33-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.33 continues the multi-year effort to migrate the network to stronger, faster cryptography. The release includes support for more signature types and preparation for Ed25519 as the default. Important bug fixes and performance improvements are included.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.32 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/11/07/0.9.32-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/11/07/0.9.32-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.32 contains a number of fixes in the router console and associated webapps (addressbook, i2psnark, and susimail). We have also changed the way we handle configured hostnames for published router infos, to eliminate some network enumeration attacks via DNS. We have added some checks in the console to resist rebinding attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.31 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/08/07/0.9.31-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/08/07/0.9.31-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The changes in this release are much more noticeable than usual! We have refreshed the router console to make it easier to understand, improve accessibility and cross-browser support, and generally tidy things up. This is the first step in a longer-term plan to make the router console more user-friendly. We have also added torrent ratings and comments support to i2psnark.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.30 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/05/03/0.9.30-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/05/03/0.9.30-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.30 contains an upgrade to Jetty 9 and Tomcat 8. The previous versions are no longer supported, and are not available in the upcoming Debian Stretch and Ubuntu Zesty releases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The router will migrate the jetty.xml configuration file for each Jetty website to the new Jetty 9 setup. This should work for recent, unmodified configurations but may not work for modified or very old setups. Verify that your Jetty website works after upgrading, and contact us on IRC if you need assistance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.29 Windows Installer Fix</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/03/04/0.9.29-windows-installer-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/03/04/0.9.29-windows-installer-fix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.9.29 Windows installer posted on our website two days ago fails during install with an Exception. We have fixed the bug and posted the new installer to our website. This does not affect upgrades from previous releases or non-Windows installers. We apologize for the issue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.29 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/02/27/0.9.29-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2017/02/27/0.9.29-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.29 contains fixes for numerous Trac tickets, including workarounds for corrupt compressed messages. We now support NTP over IPv6. We&amp;rsquo;ve added preliminary Docker support. We now have translated man pages. We now pass same-origin Referer headers through the HTTP proxy. There are more fixes for Java 9, although we do not yet recommend Java 9 for general use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.28 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/12/12/0.9.28-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/12/12/0.9.28-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.28 contains fixes for over 25 Trac tickets, and updates for a number of bundled software packages including Jetty. There are fixes for the IPv6 peer testing feature introduced last release. We continue improvements to detect and block peers that are potentially malicious. There are preliminary fixes for Java 9, although we do not yet recommend Java 9 for general use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P will be at 33C3, please stop by our table and give us your ideas on how to improve the network. We will review our 2017 roadmap and priorities 2017 at the Congress.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.27 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/10/17/0.9.27-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/10/17/0.9.27-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.27 contains a number of bug fixes. The updated GMP library for crypto acceleration, which was bundled in the 0.9.26 release for new installs and Debian builds only, is now included in the in-network update for 0.9.27. There are improvements in IPv6 transports, SSU peer testing, and hidden mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We updated a number of plugins during I2P Summer and your router will automatically update them after restart.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.26 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/06/07/0.9.26-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/06/07/0.9.26-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P is now a proposed site on Stack Exchange! Please commit to using it so the beta phase can begin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.26 contains a major upgrade to our native crypto library, a new addressbook subscription protocol with signatures, and major improvements to the Debian/Ubuntu packaging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For crypto, we have upgraded to GMP 6.0.0, and added support for newer processors, which will speed up crypto operations considerably. Also, we are now using constant-time GMP functions to prevent side-channel attacks. For caution, the GMP changes are enabled for new installs and Debian/Ubuntu builds only; we will include them for in-net updates in the 0.9.27 release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.25 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/03/22/0.9.25-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/03/22/0.9.25-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.25 contains a major new version of SAM, v3.3, to support sophisticated multiprotocol applications. It adds QR codes for sharing hidden service addresses with others, and &amp;ldquo;identicon&amp;rdquo; images for visually distinguishing addresses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve added a new &amp;ldquo;router family&amp;rdquo; configuration page in the console, to make it easier to declare that your group of routers is run by a single person. There are several changes to increase the capacity of the network and hopefully improve tunnel build success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.24 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/01/27/0.9.24-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2016/01/27/0.9.24-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.24 contains a new version of SAM (v3.2) and numerous bug fixes and efficiency improvements. Note that this release is the first to require Java 7. Please update to Java 7 or 8 as soon as possible. Your router will not automatically update if you are using Java 6.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To prevent the problems caused by the ancient commons-logging library, we have removed it. This will cause very old I2P-Bote plugins (0.2.10 and below, signed by HungryHobo) to crash if they have IMAP enabled. The recommended fix is to replace your old I2P-Bote plugin with the current one signed by str4d.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.23 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/11/19/0.9.23-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/11/19/0.9.23-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello I2P! This is the first release signed by me (str4d), after 49 releases signed by zzz. This is an important test of our redundancy for all things, including people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;housekeeping&#34;&gt;Housekeeping&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My signing key has been in router updates for over two years (since 0.9.9), so if you are on a recent version of I2P this update should be just as easy as every other update. However, if you are running an older version than 0.9.9, you will first need to manually update to a recent version. Once you have manually updated, your router will then find and download the 0.9.23 update as usual.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.22 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/09/12/0.9.22-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/09/12/0.9.22-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.22 contains fixes for i2psnark getting stuck before completion, and begins the migration of router infos to new, stronger Ed25519 signatures. To reduce network churn, your router will have only a small probability of converting to Ed25519 at each restart. When it does rekey, expect to see lower bandwidth usage for a couple of days as it reintegrates into the network with its new identity. If all goes well, we will accelerate the rekeying process in the next release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.21 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/07/31/0.9.21-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/07/31/0.9.21-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-details&#34;&gt;Update details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.21 contains several changes to add capacity to the network, increase the efficiency of the floodfills, and use bandwidth more effectively. We have migrated the shared clients tunnels to ECDSA signatures and added a DSA fallback using the new &amp;ldquo;multisession&amp;rdquo; capability for those sites that don&amp;rsquo;t support ECDSA.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The speakers and the schedule of the I2PCon in Toronto 2015 have been announced. Have a look on the I2PCon page for details. Reserve your seat on Eventbrite.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.20 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/06/02/0.9.20-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/06/02/0.9.20-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.20 contains many important bug fixes, and several changes to increase floodfill capacity in the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Routers configured for 32-64 KB of shared bandwidth may now become floodfill, and routers configured for 512 KB or more of shared bandwidth will have higher connection limits. These changes may cause your router to use more resources. If the router becomes too busy, the best way to reduce usage is to lower the bandwidth settings in your console. If that doesn&amp;rsquo;t help, you may now disable automatic floodfill on the advanced configuration page in the console.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.19 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/04/12/0.9.19-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/04/12/0.9.19-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.19 has several fixes and improvements for floodfill performance. Many of you saw high CPU usage after 0.9.18 was released. This was caused by a combination of increased encryption usage, the big influx of Vuze users into the network, reduced floodfills due to tighter performance requirements, and some longstanding bugs. Things should be a lot better after most of the network has updated. As always, the best way to reduce CPU usage is to lower your bandwidth limits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.18 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/02/22/0.9.18-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2015/02/22/0.9.18-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.18 contains several bug fixes and performance improvements. We have shortened the startup time, and reduced latency throughout our network protocols. We&amp;rsquo;ve increased the default connection limits for the fastest routers, and reduced the thread usage in i2ptunnel. UPnP fixes should improve handling of external device changes. CPU usage in high-bandwidth routers may be reduced thanks to some NTCP fixes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.17 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/11/30/0.9.17-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/11/30/0.9.17-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.17 is primarily a bugfix release, but it also continues our migration to stronger cryptographic signatures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have moved the news feed system used for the news on your console and the latest router version indication to a signed format using RSA 4096-bit keys for enhanced security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New eepsites and servers will be ECDSA-signed by default, if ECDSA is available. There is now a warning in the console sidebar if ECDSA is not available. For RedHat users, we have reports of successful installs of the BouncyCastle Provider (bcprov) jar to add ECDSA support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.16 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/11/01/0.9.16-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/11/01/0.9.16-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.16 is a significant step forward in our plan to migrate from DSA to ECDSA and then EdDSA cryptographic signatures, and makes several other changes to increase your anonymity and security. Client tunnels for standard, IRC, and SOCKS IRC will use ECDSA signatures by default. In addition, we&amp;rsquo;ve fixed a large number of serious bugs, including console lockups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Changes in router data structures will require i2pcontrol plugin users to update to version 0.0.9.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.15 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/09/20/0.9.15-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/09/20/0.9.15-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.15 adds preliminary support for Ed25519 EdDSA signatures. It includes a new persistent configuration backend for i2psnark and fixes several issues with i2psnark&amp;rsquo;s handling of file names. There are several improvements to speed up SAM. Plugins now support stronger signatures in the su3 file format. Plugin installation via the console, which was disabled in 0.9.14, is re-enabled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have supported ECDSA signatures since 0.9.12, and we would like to start using ECDSA by default. Unfortunately, some of you are still running older I2P versions, and for others, their distribution or Java runtime does not support ECDSA. Red Hat (RHEL, Fedora) distributions are reported to be missing ECDSA. Some have fixed the Java issues by upgrading from Java 6 to Java 7; others have had success with installing the &amp;ldquo;unlimited strength policy files&amp;rdquo;. We&amp;rsquo;ve added information about missing crypto to the log file and the /logs page in the console. After you update to 0.9.15, please check if you are missing ECDSA support, and attempt to fix it if necessary. This is particularly important for those that run popular eepsites and services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.14.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/08/09/0.9.14.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/08/09/0.9.14.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.14.1 includes fixes for the &amp;ldquo;Add Torrent&amp;rdquo; form in i2psnark and some other web forms. We&amp;rsquo;ve restored the ability to install plugins via the console, but you must first edit your router.config file (in ~/.i2p/ or /var/lib/i2p/i2p-config/ or %APPDATA%\I2P) to add the line routerconsole.enablePluginInstall=true. Other rarely-used advanced features that were removed in 0.9.14 may be restored by adding the line routerconsole.advanced=true.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, if configured with the default &amp;ldquo;Download and Verify&amp;rdquo;, the router will automatically download the update and display a button to restart. However, due to a bug in 0.9.14, if your update is configured for &amp;ldquo;Notify only&amp;rdquo;, the download button will not be displayed. You must change your configuration to &amp;ldquo;Download and Verify&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Download, Verify, and Restart&amp;rdquo; to update.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.9.14 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/07/26/i2p-0.9.14-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/07/26/i2p-0.9.14-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.14 includes critical fixes for XSS and remote execution vulnerabilities reported by Exodus Intelligence. As an added precaution, we have disabled several advanced configuration features in the router console, including installation of new plugins. We plan to re-enable these in a future release after additional review.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to I2P library changes, I2P-Bote users must upgrade their plugin to version 0.2.10 to work with I2P 0.9.14. Your router should update the plugin automatically after the router restarts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.9.13 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/05/22/i2p-0.9.13-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/05/22/i2p-0.9.13-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.13 includes fixes for firewalled routers, netdb lookup improvements, and a big SusiMail update. Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s also the usual collection of bug fixes and translation updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;zzz has updated his GPG keys, and the release files are signed with his new keys. His new key fingerprint is:&#xA;2D3D 2D03 910C 6504 C121 0C65 EE60 C0C8 EE72 56A8&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.12 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/03/31/0.9.12-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/03/31/0.9.12-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P now requires Java 6 or higher. We strongly recommend that you upgrade to Java 7. If you are still using Java 5, you must upgrade your Java before installing I2P 0.9.12.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0.9.12 adds preliminary support for ECDSA-signed Destinations. It contains several fixes for the handling of Delivery Status Messages (acknowledgements) and those messages are now end-to-end encrypted for increased security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have upgraded to Jetty 8. Jetty 8 is almost identical to Jetty 7, so there are no complex configuration file conversions as there have been in past Jetty upgrades. No manual changes should be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.11 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/02/08/0.9.11-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/02/08/0.9.11-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.11 continues improving LeaseSet lookup and storage to prevent an attacker from correlating a Destination with a Router. It adds support for the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.subgraph.com/orchid.html&#34;&gt;Orchid&lt;/a&gt; outproxy plugin which is available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://plugins.i2p/plugins/orchid/&#34;&gt;plugins.i2p&lt;/a&gt;. There is a reduction in memory usage due to fixes in the transports. We have some I2CP protocol improvements that will provide better lookup facilities and authorization protection for external clients. Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s also the usual collection of bug fixes. All users should update.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.10 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/01/22/0.9.10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/01/22/0.9.10-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.10 changes the mechanism for doing LeaseSet lookups, making it more difficult for an attacker to correlate a Destination with a Router. It also fixes character encoding bugs in susimail, and includes lots of other bug fixes and translation updates. Most of you will update via torrent, using the new &amp;ldquo;su3&amp;rdquo; update format with stronger keys.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recently attended &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.ccc.de/congress/2013/wiki/Main_Page&#34;&gt;30C3&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://realworldcrypto.wordpress.com/&#34;&gt;Real World Crypto&lt;/a&gt;, making several new connections and formulating &lt;a href=&#34;http://zzz.i2p&#34;&gt;big plans&lt;/a&gt; for 2014. Thanks to those who supported our attendance with their &lt;a href=&#34;http://i2p-projekt.i2p/donate&#34;&gt;donations&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syndie 1.105b Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/01/21/syndie-1.105b-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2014/01/21/syndie-1.105b-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first stable release since February 2013. It is essentially the same as 1.104b-7-rc, with some translation updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All binaries and source packages are at &lt;a href=&#34;https://syndie.de/download&#34;&gt;syndie.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.syndie.i2p/download.html&#34;&gt;syndie.i2p&lt;/a&gt;. Plugins are available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://plugins.i2p/plugins/syndie/&#34;&gt;plugins.i2p&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://stats.i2p/i2p/plugins/&#34;&gt;stats.i2p&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those of you upgrading from 1.103b, you will find syndie startup and shutdown much faster due to the new version of HSQLDB.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have a large database or an identity you wish to preserve, you may wish to back up your entire ~/.syndie directory before you start. The upgrade process does make its own backup, however you may find it easier to use your own backup if the upgrade fails.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.9 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/12/07/0.9.9-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/12/07/0.9.9-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.9 fixes a number of bugs in the netdb, streaming, and i2ptunnel, and starts work on a year-long plan to increase the strength of the cryptographic signing algorithms used in the router, and support multiple algorithms and key lengths simultaneously. Automatic update files will now be signed with 4096-bit RSA keys.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We now support SSL between your router and your servers for security. See &lt;a href=&#34;http://zzz.i2p/topics/1495&#34;&gt;this development thread&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that you update to this release. The best way to maintain security and help the network is to run the latest release. Several members of the I2P team will be at 30C3 in Hamburg this year. Come say hello and ask for an I2P sticker. Thanks to everyone for their support this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.8.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/10/02/0.9.8.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/10/02/0.9.8.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.8.1 fixes a problem with updating to 0.9.8 on Windows for some people. New installs and non-Windows platforms are not affected, however all platforms will automatically update even if running 0.9.8.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href=&#34;http://trac.i2p2.i2p/ticket/1056&#34;&gt;Trac ticket&lt;/a&gt; for details and workarounds. See &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/blog/2013-09-30-0.9.8-release/&#34;&gt;the 0.9.8 release notes&lt;/a&gt; for information on IPv6 and other changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to recent attacks, logins are disabled on &lt;a href=&#34;http://trac.i2p2.i2p/&#34;&gt;Trac&lt;/a&gt; and new registrations are disabled on &lt;a href=&#34;http://zzz.i2p/&#34;&gt;zzz.i2p&lt;/a&gt;. Until those services are restored, please report all bugs on IRC freenode or IRC2P #i2p-dev.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.8 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/09/30/0.9.8-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/09/30/0.9.8-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.8 includes the long-awaited support for IPv6. It&amp;rsquo;s enabled by default, but of course you need a public IPv6 address to use it. Configuration is on the &amp;rsquo;network&amp;rsquo; configuration tab in your console. We also have anonymity improvements including padding of SSU packets and longer router private keys.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;30% of you will update via in-network torrent in this update cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ipv6-details&#34;&gt;IPv6 Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IPv6 is enabled and preferred by default. If you have a public IPv6 address and you are connecting to another router with a published IPv6 address, it will connect via IPv6. There is a new IPv6 configuration section on /confignet in the router console. If IPv6 is causing problems you may disable it there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.7.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/08/10/0.9.7.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/08/10/0.9.7.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This unscheduled release disables the RouterInfo verification messages that were used in the attack published in the UCSB paper, which should make correlating a LeaseSet and a Router much more difficult. We have also included a limited number of other fixes listed below. Our 0.9.8 release, which will include IPv6 support, is still on-schedule for late September.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, we recommend that all users update to this release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;anonymity-improvements&#34;&gt;Anonymity Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Disable RouterInfo verification messages&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Extend inbound tunnel expiration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2prouter: bashism fix&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2psnark: increase max piece size, mime type updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;New reseed host&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;New update hosts, thanks Meeh and dg&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Streaming: RTO changes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Updater: Increase update-via-torrent to 30 percent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;UPnP fix for some hardware&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;293f445196a2f35c4d580f65b548135399e1f4443450b5ecf1cc53b1203fdad1  i2pinstall_0.9.7.1_windows.exe&#xA;9fae874a4d680f50f5efd7be70cfcf55f2f4687e011bde9c4b4899bafb002e97  i2pinstall_0.9.7.1.jar&#xA;7b73bdb23c53798054741cbaa4e7d8cce832ee566fbb17df0c803d0c22d099e1  i2psource_0.9.7.1.tar.bz2&#xA;69ca22a77a2de87f726d86555317f8688891d31f5312cf71d5a43febe2729b38  i2pupdate_0.9.7.1.zip&#xA;f59c9c80349c328b3e912113a3842146f647ff22ae323cef6b1e56a23f8c8cf1  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;52d1f32e2a72091da10312853e5df6bced12cb97770ba20732f2d9d6c4d2f5fe  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.7 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/07/15/0.9.7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/07/15/0.9.7-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.7 includes significant bug fixes and improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, class &amp;lsquo;N&amp;rsquo; routers (those with a minimumum of 128 KBytes/sec of shared bandwidth) will automatically become floodfill (previously it was only &amp;lsquo;O&amp;rsquo; routers with 256 KBps). This will increase the floodfill population for additional resistance to certain attacks (see below). Floodfill routers don&amp;rsquo;t consume much additional bandwidth, but they do tend to use additional memory and concurrent connections. If you do not wish your router to become floodfill, set the advanced configuration router.floodfillParticipant=false.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.6 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/05/28/0.9.6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/05/28/0.9.6-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.6 includes bug fixes and an update from Jetty 6.1.26 (2010-11-10) to Jetty 7.6.10 (2013-03-12). See below for important information on the Jetty update. The Jetty 7 series is actively maintained and we plan to stay current with it in future I2P releases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most users will update via HTTP. Those running development builds will attempt to update via the experimental in-network bittorrent with i2psnark. We&amp;rsquo;ve fixed some bugs that will enable more users to update via torrent in the 0.9.7 update cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.5 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/03/08/0.9.5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2013/03/08/0.9.5-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.5 includes bug fixes and defenses for some issues and vulnerabilities that are being investigated by researchers at UCSB. We continue to work with them on additional improvements. This is a good opportunity to remind the community that while our network continues to grow rapidly, it is still relatively small. There may be multiple weaknesses or bugs that could compromise your anonymity. Help us grow the network by spreading the word and contributing where you can.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.4 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/12/17/0.9.4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/12/17/0.9.4-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.4 includes a fix for a network capacity bug, introduced in 0.9.2, that was reducing network performance and reliability. It also includes major changes in the in-network update system, and adds the capability to update via in-network torrents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We fixed several bugs in the i2psnark DHT implementation that was introduced last release. For those of you using console or http proxy passwords, we converted to the more-secure digest method and improved the security for console forms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.3 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/10/27/0.9.3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/10/27/0.9.3-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.3 includes extensive low-level changes to the queueing of messages in the router. We implement the CoDel Active Queue Management (AQM) algorithm. We also unify the queueing and priority mechanisms in the transports to aid diagnosis and reduce network latency. Work continues on fixing UDP transport bugs and making UDP more resistant to attacks. There are more changes to improve the performance of the router and reduce its memory usage. Also, we enable i2psnark&amp;rsquo;s DHT support, introduced last release, by default.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/09/21/0.9.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/09/21/0.9.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.2 includes extensive low-level changes to improve the performance and efficiency of the router. We have updated our UPnP library, to hopefully make UPnP work for more people. I2PSnark now has DHT support, but it is not yet enabled by default, as we plan to do more testing during the upcoming 0.9.3 development cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, there&amp;rsquo;s also lots of bug fixes in this release, so updating is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/downloads/&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/07/30/0.9.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/07/30/0.9.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.9.1 includes a large number of bug fixes in i2psnark, some streaming lib improvements, home page changes, new themes, and translation updates. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/downloads/&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i2psnark&#34;&gt;I2PSnark&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix several bugs in downloading torrents with skipped files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix places where rarest-first was not honored&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix handling of encoded magnet links&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additional inbound connection limits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Immediate closing of connections with handshake errors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blocklist peers with multiple handshake errors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delay &amp;ldquo;ballooning&amp;rdquo; files on disk until required, to speed torrent adds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Store partial pieces in temp files to greatly reduce memory usage when leeching&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Remove peers restriction when leeching torrents with large pieces&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improve configuration of open and private trackers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Prevent configuration of default trackers as private&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved display and control of torrent file downloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduced number of threads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Faster startup and shutdown of torrents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Allow clearing of message box&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;New light theme&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Torrent info page updates and cleanups&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix problems with restarted torrents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delay tunnel close at shutdown to ensure trackers are notified&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Better UI behavior during tunnel startup and shutdown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Prevent shutdown hangs caused by buggy plugins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix for Raspberry Pi crashing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix rare job queue hang&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix routing key modifier rarely not updating at midnight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix excessive padding in some AES-encrypted messages&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix occasional gunzip failures&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Several fixes to streaming lib to speed recovery after dropped packets and improve retransmit behavior&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix bug that reduced reuse of tunnels&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ports are now passed through the SOCKS and HTTP proxies to support eepsite virtual hosts. See &lt;a href=&#34;http://zzz.i&#34;&gt;http://zzz.i&lt;/a&gt;2p/topics/1182 for setup instructions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I2PTunnel configuration changes now take effect immediately. No tunnel restart required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Summary bar iframe removed, refresh is now via Javascript only&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduce netDB flood redundancy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduce stats publishing frequency&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Minor router console changes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;New Hungarian and Greek translations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Completed Italian translation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Updates to Dutch, Finnish, French, German, Spanish, and Swedish translations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Update geoip to Maxmind 2012-07-04&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Theme updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Theme support for SusiMail and SudiDNS; new dark themes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I2PTunnel and SusiDNS now iframed with summary bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Console home page now shows news summary in summary bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Console home page icon updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Console summary bar now configurable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change the HTTP proxy error code from 404 to 500&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cleanups for efficiency in netdb and I2CP&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increase timeout for internal uses of eepget to improve reliability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;0727af83988e82f32e0972a9e12c72ac14c3c0da0815c5902193d6b13d356371  i2pinstall_0.9.1_windows.exe&#xA;39c19c0df042ad231a14fdf1c20e4927651a2af0f0cf734b46eba0d2b8419314  i2pinstall_0.9.1.jar&#xA;8603c928a210ced77b6498bf8ee07cb000be9641adc389b34c3c8a10ac4f0677  i2psource_0.9.1.tar.bz2&#xA;136b74435b93aededef5884d39cfbc513f57184b74c8481580bcd5324aa23b1a  i2pupdate_0.9.1.zip&#xA;4f07fee850d56fada06f0aeabb5bb46c6172bad72411e07bf4f6a8e0d76d8acd  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;c039b423983789d914a1d02d3703b3c1aa36c87165e132419ff39b5d184ef480  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.9 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/05/02/0.9-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/05/02/0.9-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.9 release concludes over a year and a half of work on the 0.8.x series, in which we greatly improved the performance and security of the router, and the scalability of the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the 0.9 release we migrate to Jetty 6 for the console and eepsite web server, and introduce a simplified router console home page. This release is network-compatible with prior releases, however see below for important information on compatibility with existing eepsites, plugins, and webapps. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.13 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/02/27/0.8.13-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/02/27/0.8.13-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.13 release contains several bug fixes and a couple of new features. We are pleased that the last release significantly improved performance, and the network is running well despite continued rapid growth. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/downloads/&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is likely to be the last release before 0.9, in which we will migrate to Jetty 6, and introduce a simplified router console home page. Monitor the news section of your the router console in the coming weeks for more information on the next release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.12 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/01/06/0.8.12-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2012/01/06/0.8.12-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.12 release fixes several message corruption bugs, some present since 2005. It also contains a redesign of the router&amp;rsquo;s congestion control, and continued optimization of CPU and memory usage. We are hopeful that these changes will improve network performance. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/downloads/&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release contains several big changes that should help network reliability and performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first two changes are fixes for major UDP packet transmission bugs, described below. The third change is fixes to the decompressor. Fixing these should eliminate a big source of message delivery failures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.11 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/11/08/0.8.11-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/11/08/0.8.11-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As you all have noticed, the unprecedented network growth starting October 5th has dramatically increased network congestion, especially on evenings (UTC) and weekends. The last two releases contained a few changes that we hoped would relieve the pressure, but unfortunately these measures have been only modest successes. The primary issue is to limit the number of direct router to-router connections in the network. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a new problem; we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on it for several years, with good results. However, the recent growth pushed us over the edge once again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.10 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/10/20/0.8.10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/10/20/0.8.10-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Release 0.8.10 includes two changes intended to reduce the number of router-to-router connections, and therefore improve tunnel build success rates and general reliability. Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s also a few bug fixes and translation updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../en/downloads/&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;RELEASE DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;major-changes&#34;&gt;Major Changes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Disable tunnel testing as it forces too many router connections&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select outbound endpoint - inbound gateway paths that are closer, using an XOR metric, to reduce router connections&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix exceptions at shutdown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix concurrency errors in SSU&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix timeout message on POST&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increase max tunnels, reduce router info expiration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add gunzip support to eepget to reduce reseed bandwidth&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Finnish, Italian, Russian, and Swedish translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;8494640d29b1b7969118169a7ae1c56bc5a07f354ec883734687bf09eef0e35c  i2pinstall_0.8.10.exe&#xA;e5832bb49f46b0b6620e8492e6fc6454de4107b84bca5a4b35461c6b7ac0575e  i2psource_0.8.10.tar.bz2&#xA;64bcd1fdd478cfda987c1d4906d94b3f20a0555bd4037aefa7a09af4f39a0e99  i2pupdate_0.8.10.zip&#xA;5620113f4e19768e15af0a9c8bc670ca443e9983a0d4868997800ee215790c51  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;39bfbfebbf77d660081fe1ce282f642fb15ed9cd170901f54a954bc986eadaf5  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.9 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/10/11/0.8.9-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/10/11/0.8.9-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.9 release has several performance improvements, and many changes to handle the continued rapid growth of the network. It uses a new iterative method for Kademlia network database lookups that should be more reliable and efficient. There are also several improvements to our SSU (UDP) transport protocol that should help reliability and efficiency. We have made several changes to improve tunnel build success rates. And, of course, there are lots of bug fixes and translation updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.8 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/08/23/0.8.8-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/08/23/0.8.8-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P release 0.8.8 enables the new hosts.txt database to speed hostname lookups and store additional information on hostname entries. It also includes improvements to speed a router&amp;rsquo;s integration on startup. There is new code to detect and react to large clock shifts that should help a router recover after suspend/resume of the computer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are new translations for Danish and Ukrainian and lots of updates in other languages. Also included are, of course, a large collection of bug fixes, performance improvements, and updates to deal with the continued rapid expansion of the network.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.7 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/06/27/0.8.7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/06/27/0.8.7-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P release 0.8.7 contains several upgrades to long-neglected components, including the Naming Services, graphing, the native CPU ID and BigInteger libraries, crypto implementations, and the wrapper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to new contributor KillYourTV who was instrumental in implementing and testing these upgrades, with additional support from sponge and hottuna.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CPU ID enhancements are by hottuna, generously funded by &lt;a href=&#34;http://relakks.com/&#34;&gt;Relakks&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://ipredator.se/&#34;&gt;Ipredator&lt;/a&gt; - thanks to Peter Sunde and Jan-Erik Fiske for their support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, for the first time, we now have an official &lt;a href=&#34;https://launchpad.net/~i2p-maintainers/&amp;#43;archive/i2p&#34;&gt;I2P Personal Package Archive (PPA) on launchpad.net&lt;/a&gt;. For those of you using Ubuntu, this offers an easy way to install I2P and keep the various components up-to-date. The I2P package offers the option of installing as a service, or it may be started on-demand as usual. This PPA is currently maintained by KillYourTV with support by other members of the development team. The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/debian&#34;&gt;Ubuntu/Debian installation instructions&lt;/a&gt; are on our website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.6 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/05/16/0.8.6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/05/16/0.8.6-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.6 release contains more peer selection defenses to resist powerful attackers, and tweaks to adjust to the recent rapid growth in the network. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;Get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! If you find a bug, please enter a report on &lt;a href=&#34;http://i2pgit.org/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/issues&#34;&gt;gitlab&lt;/a&gt;. We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p-dev.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../download.html&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release details:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Strip trailing nulls from malformed UPnP responses from devices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix a cause of excess tunnel creation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Peer organization and selection changes to resist fast tier enumeration and manipulation by attackers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increase floodfill pool and decrease router info expiration time to adjust to recent network growth&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;0bd9927d607d2ac9986732b29b1c4b15a0fbb3521b2fa14dded10d5a57333efc  i2pinstall_0.8.6.exe&#xA;d784ab7ccfdf60f7ad71d625cd88c88c9290d3aeecfa419e03a7930e3faa72d0  i2psource_0.8.6.tar.bz2&#xA;e7153b4635c79b5c2592adb7597e4c4fd8bc38c87fb34925fad6a965f4d83de8  i2pupdate_0.8.6.zip&#xA;28af7bc483e6ae91325771ce368ba28cb65ccdafef739336454720578864f326  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;dcff98e499122b7b6fc4e7dd7fddb1d8a45684460246da5b4eb5eeb3b1ed351f  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.5 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/04/18/0.8.5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/04/18/0.8.5-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.5 release contains a few bug fixes and performance improvements, and lots of translation updates. As usual, upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;Get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! If you find a bug, please enter a report on &lt;a href=&#34;http://i2pgit.org/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/issues&#34;&gt;gitlab&lt;/a&gt;. We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p-dev.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../download.html&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release details:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lots of router console HTML fixes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2psnark magnet handling fixes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SusiMail Translation support by &amp;ldquo;duck&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuing work on the Arabic translation by &amp;ldquo;hamada&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Completion of the French translation by &amp;ldquo;magma&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Completion of the Spanish translation by &amp;ldquo;punkibastardo&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;user&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Other translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Better support for text-mode browsers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Profile display improvements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tunnel build request queue limiting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Require nonce to change console language&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2psnark improved logging of errors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i2psnark improved metainfo handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the reseed server as a backup time source&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change profile file extension from .dat to .txt.gz&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change all i2ptunnels to 3 hops for new installs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add all bogons to blocklist for new installs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More efficient use of entropy for padding&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;6ae6b196352e1053c4e7b91edc575330d108ff9abfc2746ea3c3b2e3fd467006  i2pinstall_0.8.5.exe&#xA;de9fa105c1335d58609689a942d3e6a508ca824fc8b27a34c1c0b09fc7e0167b  i2psource_0.8.5.tar.bz2&#xA;7e4c1835dfd7aaa42d84cf4646f5858a37efa027f43a26eb98360e3cb4750ac8  i2pupdate_0.8.5.zip&#xA;efea978f3e4e955b9afa05847dc4ebb83c8df3651adeb717769e32a908bc5f53  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;1b6eca94b7938f5c61c26b4482c89919bdfbc7c41aee7735f8f561c01c3a29d3  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.4 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/03/02/0.8.4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/03/02/0.8.4-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.4 release contains some performance improvements and important bug fixes. Also, i2psnark now supports magnet links. As usual, upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;Get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! If you find a bug, please enter a report on &lt;a href=&#34;http://i2pgit.org/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/issues&#34;&gt;gitlab&lt;/a&gt;. We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p-dev.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../download.html&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;release-details&#34;&gt;Release details:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix a severe memory leak in router I2CP session management that caused router crashes for people running the Robert bittorrent client&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fix a bug from 0.8.2 that filtered cookies in the HTTP Server tunnel, causing authentication problems for some eepsites (I2P Sites)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Several fixes for rare NPEs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i2psnark&#34;&gt;I2PSnark&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Magnet and &amp;ldquo;maggot&amp;rdquo; link support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Peer Exchange&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Metadata transfer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Details page enhancements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bandwidth limiter improvements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bug fixes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More performance improvements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adjustment to peer selection, to hopefully use more of the available network capacity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translation updates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Start of a new Arabic translation by &amp;lsquo;hamada&amp;rsquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sha256-checksums&#34;&gt;SHA256 Checksums:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;2b9f82b2c236cedcb6d394557a366ea3e181ca244461375a810709b2f7d4e881  i2pinstall_0.8.4.exe&#xA;e454880a753963361e43d65da69542c4e8caa62d2646e8ce851b2f95fd9e735c  i2psource_0.8.4.tar.bz2&#xA;5c6632b5f97e02296ad2d3d5f108b472d6766967a037d96421ad36fa5f2e60a9  i2pupdate_0.8.4.zip&#xA;155cd3ca7d174c30367dfa147b11a0c55fb6e85680a0aeda126afcb5e141db42  i2pupdate.su2&#xA;465060129520ad115a3823e625def94b8ebafdd28c6ab9b27e125afed70cf851  i2pupdate.sud&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.3 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/01/24/0.8.3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2011/01/24/0.8.3-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.3 release contains several performance improvements, including reduction of threads and memory usage, and faster I2CP (client-router) communication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is also new SSL router console support, a new reseed configuration page including HTTP proxy support for those behind restrictive firewalls, a new I2CP configuration section including I2CP-over-SSL support for remote clients, a new server connection limits and blacklist configuration section for enhanced DoS protection, and a new HTTP proxy jump server configuration section so you may easily add alternative jump servers. Statistics are now limited by default to reduce memory usage; the full set of statistics may be re-enabled on the stats configuration page. There are also bug fixes, of course, so as usual, upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/12/22/0.8.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/12/22/0.8.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.2 release includes extensive bug fixes and theme updates in the router and in i2psnark. There are also optimizations to reduce memory usage in i2psnark. The HTTP and SOCKS proxies now support local and remote authorization. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P will be at 27C3 in Berlin the week of December 27th. Look for the I2P people there and ask for I2P stickers!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;Get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! If you find a bug, please enter a report on &lt;a href=&#34;http://i2pgit.org/i2p-hackers/i2p.i2p/issues&#34;&gt;gitlab&lt;/a&gt;. We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/11/15/0.8.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/11/15/0.8.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.8.1 release contains the usual collection of bug fixes and performance tweaks. There is also a new i2psnark theme and several translation updates. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. Give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../download.html&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Release details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.8 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/07/12/0.8-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/07/12/0.8-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In early 2009, shortly after our attendance at 25C3, we released version 0.7 of the I2P Anonymous Network. Over the next 15 releases in 18 months we have worked to improve the usability of the I2P software and increase its performance, security, and reliability - all while dealing with unprecedented growth in the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In recognition of these accomplishments, we are declaring the start of the 0.8 series. The 0.8 release is fully compatible with all 0.7.x releases. This release contains several bugfixes, a new Dutch translation, and completion of the German translation. As always, users are encouraged to upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.14 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/06/07/0.7.14-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/06/07/0.7.14-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.14 release contains the usual collection of bug fixes and performance tweaks. There are also some i2psnark improvements and more fixes for plugins. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. Give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Files are available on the &lt;a href=&#34;../../../download.html&#34;&gt;download page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Release details:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.13 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/04/27/0.7.13-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/04/27/0.7.13-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.13 release contains several changes and bug fixes to improve performance. It also includes improvements for the plugin support that was introduced in the last release. The new, smaller tunnel build message is enabled, to reduce overhead and increase build success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, there is the usual assortment of bug fixes as well. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please help grow the network. Give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.12 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/03/15/0.7.12-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/03/15/0.7.12-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.12 release contains support for user-generated plugins. These plugins may contain console web applications, themes, translations, or standalone programs. Some plugins are already available for testing. We are hopeful this support will enable rapid development of innovative i2p applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The release fixes the blank-page bug when an eepsite(I2P Site) is not reachable, and also improves handling of clock skews and IP changes. It adds support for a new, smaller tunnel build message, that will be tested in this release and enabled in the next release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.11 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/02/15/0.7.11-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/02/15/0.7.11-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.11 release fixes several issues, some related to clocks, which prevented new routers from quickly integrating into the network. It also fixes the installer for 64-bit Windows. The release includes an update to &lt;a href=&#34;http://old.nabble.com/jetty-5.1.15,-6.1.18-and-7.0.0.M2-td23652819.html&#34;&gt;Jetty 5.1.15&lt;/a&gt; to fix &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kb.cert.org/vuls/id/402580&#34;&gt;this vulnerability&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As usual, the release contains more anonymity and performance improvements, and an assortment of bug fixes. Upgrading is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt;, spread the word, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.10 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/01/22/0.7.10-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/01/22/0.7.10-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.7.10 closes some recently-discovered vulnerabilities related to the way routers communicate with floodfill peers. Network database stores and verifies are moved from exploratory to client tunnels, and are encrypted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, to improve anonymity, router&amp;rsquo;s fast peer set is now limited to a maximum of 30. The release also fixes a bug causing Windows installs to fail when the install or user path contained a &amp;ldquo;\r&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;\n&amp;rdquo;. Upgrading is recommended. Please give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.7.9 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/01/12/0.7.9-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2010/01/12/0.7.9-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;0.7.9 fixes several longstanding bugs causing message corruption. We are hopeful that network performance will improve once it is widely deployed. There are other changes that should help router reachability and tunnel build success rates. The release also includes additional translation support, and a full Russian translation by &amp;ldquo;forget&amp;rdquo; which was sponsored by &amp;ldquo;russiansponsor&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are more changes to reduce memory and CPU usage, and other bug fixes. Upgrading is recommended. Please give the developers feedback on IRC #i2p or &lt;a href=&#34;http://forum.i2p2.de/&#34;&gt;forum.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/getinvolved.html&#34;&gt;get involved&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/donate.html&#34;&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt;! We are still looking for help on new and existing translations. Please volunteer on IRC #i2p.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.8 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/12/08/i2p-0.7.8-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/12/08/i2p-0.7.8-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Release 0.7.8 contains initial support for router console translations, and changes to the floodfill system which lay the foundation for supporting large growth in the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To prevent easy blocking of I2P by malicious firewalls, the release randomizes the I2P port for new installs. For existing installs, please help those who are vulnerable to blocking by changing UDP from 8887 to a random port on and adjusting your firewall if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.7 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/10/12/i2p-0.7.7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/10/12/i2p-0.7.7-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P version 0.7.7 contains several anonymity improvements. The use of session keys for crypto was completely reworked, and I2PSnark now uses its own tunnels for tracker communication. Work continues on improving the router console, including conformance to HTML standards and better support of UTF-8.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Work also continues on increasing speeds, both by reducing the number of session keys transferred, by improving the methods of dropping messages during overload, and by reducing drops by high-bandwidth routers. There is a new unsigned update option for those of you that would like automatic updates to bleeding-edge development versions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.6 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/07/31/i2p-0.7.6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/07/31/i2p-0.7.6-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I2P version 0.7.6 contains additional fixes for network stability issues related to tunnel building and connection limits. While the 0.7.5 release greatly improved the congestion that appeared UTC evenings and weekends, it was not eliminated; this release should improve the situation further.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This version also has new console themes by dr|z3d, which may be selected on the new UI configuration page. Sorry, the new themes are not available for IE browsers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.5 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/06/29/i2p-0.7.5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/06/29/i2p-0.7.5-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-075&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7.5&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P version 0.7.5 foremost addresses network stability issues by adjusting how exploratory tunnels are built if a router nears its connection limit, and also by distinguishing between connected peers and other non-failing peers while picking them for inclusion in tunnels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This version also delivers fixes to installer behaviour on Windows, to the Router Console, NTCP transport and UPnP mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, version 0.7.5 changes the &amp;ldquo;news.xml&amp;rdquo; file location where I2P routers check whether a new version is available. Instead of the old URL (&lt;a href=&#34;http://complication.i&#34;&gt;http://complication.i&lt;/a&gt;2p/news.xml) a new location (&lt;a href=&#34;http://echelon.i&#34;&gt;http://echelon.i&lt;/a&gt;2p/i2p/news.xml) will be used. If your router uses default updater settings, it will start using the new URL automatically. If not, you will need to visit &amp;ldquo;configupdate.jsp&amp;rdquo; on the Router Console, and change it manually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.4 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/06/13/i2p-0.7.4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/06/13/i2p-0.7.4-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-074&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7.4&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P version 0.7.4 introduces notable new features like GeoIP capability and UPnP support. While the former can become a basis for geographically aware tunnel-building, the latter should immediately enable more routers to accept inbound TCP connections, helping distribute workload more evenly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inbound NTCP is now enabled automaticaly if the router does not appear firewalled, and default bandwidth limits for new installations are increased.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, multiple bugfixes and updates are included, addressing issues with the NTCP transport, BOB protocol, connection limiting, behaviour of new I2PTunnel options and the SusiDNS user interface. Improvements to the Router Console are likewise included. Updating is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.3 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/05/18/i2p-0.7.3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/05/18/i2p-0.7.3-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-073&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7.3&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I2P version 0.7.3 contains several buxfixes and improvements, includes a lot of maintenance work and new versions of both the SAM and BOB application gateway protocols.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A patch to I2P&amp;rsquo;s internal web server Jetty is included to correct SusiDNS behaviour on Windows. The way I2P nodes volunteer to participate in the Network Database is changed to avoid too many doing this simultaneously, and creation of new participating tunnels is now throttled before messages in existing tunnels start to get dropped.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/04/19/i2p-0.7.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/04/19/i2p-0.7.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-072&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7.2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.2 release fixes multiple bugs and potential problems in I2P, while preparing ground for new functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Threading issues with the SimpleTimer class should no longer occur, the NTCP transport should no longer encounter null pointer exceptions, and &amp;ldquo;abandoned&amp;rdquo; tunnels should finish operation correctly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Support is added for accessing the Router Console over IPv6, a new message type enables I2CP applications to query the router&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth limits, an experimental desktop interface for managing the router is included for the first time (but not enabled automatically yet) and participation of a single peer in too many tunnels is prevented to improve reliability and safety.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7.1 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/03/29/i2p-0.7.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/03/29/i2p-0.7.1-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-071&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7.1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.7.1 release optimizes I2P towards better performance and introduces new features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multiple bugs are fixed, replacements to the SimpleTimer class should waste less time on object locking. Some old components are dropped and several classes refactored to avoid repeating code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Support for encrypted LeaseSets (for creation of links over I2P which an adversary cannot obstruct by attacking its gateways) becomes more complete. New tunnel types like IRC server tunnels and new options like delayed start and idling of tunnels also gain support, along with improved usability of the I2P Socks proxy mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.7 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/01/25/i2p-0.7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2009/01/25/i2p-0.7-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-07&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.7&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.7 release adds stability and flexibility to I2PSnark,&#xA;which can hopefully be used to distribute I2P updates in future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The I2P router gets fixes and optimizations to various&#xA;transport-level and streaming issues, network exploration,&#xA;NetDB performance and the UDP introducer system. Among other features,&#xA;the new release offers better connection limiting, higher tolerance&#xA;to &amp;ldquo;out of memory&amp;rdquo; exceptions in helper applications, and an&#xA;experimental new address system using Base32 hashes&#xA;of destination keys (&amp;quot;.b32.i2p&amp;quot; URLs).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.5 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/12/01/i2p-0.6.5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/12/01/i2p-0.6.5-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-065&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.5&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.5 release introduces new components,&#xA;drops some old ones (like the old TCP transport)&#xA;and has been optimized to perform better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The BOB (Basic Open Bridge) protocol is introduced,&#xA;for use by client applications which cannot import&#xA;I2CP libraries directly. This deprecates the old&#xA;SAM protocol which was previously used in such cases.&#xA;For now however, BOB is not started automatically yet on&#xA;new installations, and SAM remains active on old installations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.4 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/10/06/i2p-0.6.4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/10/06/i2p-0.6.4-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-064&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.4&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.4 release adds performance and stability improvements.&#xA;Floodfill peers which are already connected, are preferred&#xA;for RouterInfo stores, and references to new floodfill peers&#xA;obtained from ordinary peers in case of shortage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Preference for already connected peers is generally increased&#xA;by considering them active. Timeouts during tunnel joins&#xA;are now counted against peer profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Improvements to the shutdown handler, tunnel builder,&#xA;router throttling, collection of tunnel pool statistics,&#xA;as well as router console and I2PSnark improvements&#xA;(and texts to explain reachability issues) are also included.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.3 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/08/26/i2p-0.6.3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/08/26/i2p-0.6.3-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-063&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.3&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.3 release introduces multiple bugfixes, optimizations&#xA;and security improvements. Routers will start monitoring the number&#xA;of well-behaved NetDB peers, volunteering as one if a shortage develops&#xA;and they can. Well-behaved NetDB nodes are preferred stronger,&#xA;and ill-behaved nodes blacklisted more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LeaseSets are handled more efficiently, new fixes should enable&#xA;the correct operation of UDP introducers. I2P also gains&#xA;preliminary support for permanent IP blocklists, and a new&#xA;peer connection limiter. Improvements to the Router Console&#xA;should make configuring client applications easier and I2PSnark&#xA;will now resist corrupt data better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.2 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/06/07/i2p-0.6.2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/06/07/i2p-0.6.2-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-062&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.2 release delivers performance and anonymity improvements.&#xA;LeaseSet data is no longer added to every end-to-end message,&#xA;reducing protocol overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unreachable peers are avoided as inbound tunnel gateways,&#xA;which helps reliability and makes it possible to use&#xA;persistent Lease selection, which in turn helps performance&#xA;by reducing out-of-order message delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sequence of peers in a tunnel is now kept in a strict order&#xA;according to XOR distance from a random value, to make it harder&#xA;for an adversary to gather statistics for a predecessor attack.&#xA;Improvements to applications like I2PSnark and the Router Console&#xA;are also introduced.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.1.33 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/04/26/i2p-0.6.1.33-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/04/26/i2p-0.6.1.33-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-06133&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.1.33&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.1.33 release contains several important bug fixes&#xA;and performance improvements in SSU reachability detection,&#xA;floodfill peer selection, tunnel peer selection, tunnel testing,&#xA;NTCP idle detection, the streaming lib, and news fetching.&#xA;It also adds secondary tracker support to i2psnark, and verification&#xA;of downloaded Jetty libraries when building from source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please upgrade as soon as you can, as these fixes&#xA;should improve the reliability of the whole network.&#xA;This release is backward compatible: if you already have&#xA;0.6.1.31 or greater installed, it will recognize the signature&#xA;on the signed update file, and you can update automatically.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.1.32 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/03/09/i2p-0.6.1.32-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/03/09/i2p-0.6.1.32-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;i2p-release-06132&#34;&gt;I2P release 0.6.1.32&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.1.32 release contains several bugfixes,&#xA;a new tunnel build algorithm from zzz which regulates&#xA;the intensity of tunnel building according to previous levels&#xA;of tunnel build success, and other performance improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release is backward compatible, and if you already have&#xA;0.6.1.31 installed, it will recognize the signature&#xA;on the signed update file (so you can update automatically).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, to ensure better distribution of load&#xA;between our 3 signed update servers, I recommend that you&#xA;perform the following optional check:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.1.31 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/02/10/i2p-0.6.1.31-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2008/02/10/i2p-0.6.1.31-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, there&amp;rsquo;s a new I2P release available for your enjoyment at&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p2.de/download.html&#34;&gt;http://www.i2p2.de/download.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 0.6.1.31 release will make the I2P release process&#xA;independent of jrandom and *.i2p.net servers.&#xA;Our new primary mirror is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.i2p2.de&#34;&gt;www.i2p2.de&lt;/a&gt;, accessible&#xA;in I2P at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.i2p2.i&#34;&gt;www.i2p2.i&lt;/a&gt;2p.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Automatic updates will hosted on several eepsites(I2P Sites),&#xA;signed by Complication, for which purpose 0.6.1.31&#xA;includes two new release verification keys.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also included are multiple bugfixes and improvements&#xA;to the automatic update mechanism, address book,&#xA;I2PSnark and IRC proxy. Support will appear for the&#xA;SAM protocol version 2.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2P 0.6.1.30 Release</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2007/10/07/i2p-0.6.1.30-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/2007/10/07/i2p-0.6.1.30-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi y&amp;rsquo;all, there&amp;rsquo;s a new I2P release available for your enjoyment at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.i2p.net/download&#34;&gt;http://www.i2p.net/download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release includes some experimental tunnel throughput enhancements, eepget fixes, network backlog handling, i2psnark fixes, among other changes. As always, a full list of changes can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;http://dev.i2p.net/cgi-bin/cvsweb.cgi/i2p/history.txt?rev=HEAD&#34;&gt;http://dev.i2p.net/cgi-bin/cvsweb.cgi/i2p/history.txt?rev=HEAD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release is backwards compatible, and upgrading shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks go to zzz and Complication for their work making all these changes happen!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;=jr&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
